Facilities and Physical Plant, Office of; Records ua331
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Office of Facilities Management Website, 2004 April 4 - 2017 May 17; 1; 268 captures
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 July 17
    Crawl Times
    start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2015-07-17T16:55:07Z
    last_resumption: None
    processing_end_date: 2015-07-22T22:02:18Z
    end_date: 2015-07-22T21:28:19Z
    elapsed_ms: 448383534
    Crawl Types
    type: MONTHLY
    recurrence_type: MONTHLY
    pdfs_only: False
    test: False
    Crawl Limits
    time_limit: 432000
    document_limit: None
    byte_limit: None
    crawl_stop_requested: None
    Crawl Results
    status: FINISHED_TIME_LIMIT
    discovered_count: 518483
    novel_count: 22064
    duplicate_count: 310947
    resumption_count: 0
    queued_count: 185472
    downloaded_count: 333011
    download_failures: 280
    warc_revisit_count: 310940
    warc_url_count: 332912
    total_data_in_kbs: 92321075
    duplicate_bytes: 89386949991
    warc_compressed_bytes: 975896456
    Crawl Technical Details
    doc_rate: 0.74
    kb_rate: 205.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 July 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 August 17
    crawl: 169175
    start_date: 2015-08-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2015-08-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-08-22T17:22:04Z
    end_date: 2015-08-22T16:57:37Z
    elapsed_ms: 432154021
    discovered_count: 580375
    novel_count: 18815
    duplicate_count: 281416
    queued_count: 280144
    downloaded_count: 300231
    download_failures: 232
    warc_revisit_count: 281408
    warc_url_count: 300140
    total_data_in_kbs: 104928074
    duplicate_bytes: 100253233235
    warc_compressed_bytes: 965534609
    doc_rate: 0.69
    kb_rate: 242.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 August 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 September 5
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 September 17
    crawl: 173356
    start_date: 2015-09-17T16:57:20Z
    original_start_date: 2015-09-17T16:57:20Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-09-23T01:24:03Z
    end_date: 2015-09-23T00:16:53Z
    elapsed_ms: 458363239
    discovered_count: 367719
    novel_count: 26001
    duplicate_count: 206766
    queued_count: 134952
    downloaded_count: 232767
    download_failures: 237
    warc_revisit_count: 206761
    warc_url_count: 232678
    total_data_in_kbs: 101606587
    duplicate_bytes: 94029637527
    warc_compressed_bytes: 157865634
    doc_rate: 0.51
    kb_rate: 221.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 September 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 November 9
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 November 17
    crawl: 183657
    start_date: 2015-11-17T17:41:09Z
    original_start_date: 2015-11-17T17:41:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-03T05:50:07Z
    end_date: 2015-11-30T19:18:26Z
    elapsed_ms: 432098049
    discovered_count: 415196
    novel_count: 17867
    duplicate_count: 229881
    queued_count: 167448
    downloaded_count: 247748
    download_failures: 242
    warc_revisit_count: 229876
    warc_url_count: 247648
    total_data_in_kbs: 61913750
    duplicate_bytes: 62091532709
    warc_compressed_bytes: 256259119
    doc_rate: 0.57
    kb_rate: 143.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 November 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 December 11
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 December 17
    crawl: 187970
    start_date: 2015-12-17T16:55:04Z
    original_start_date: 2015-12-17T16:55:04Z
    processing_end_date: 2015-12-22T21:57:26Z
    end_date: 2015-12-22T21:40:44Z
    elapsed_ms: 449129872
    discovered_count: 304232
    novel_count: 13877
    duplicate_count: 191764
    queued_count: 98591
    downloaded_count: 205641
    download_failures: 234
    warc_revisit_count: 191759
    warc_url_count: 205547
    total_data_in_kbs: 60257781
    duplicate_bytes: 60588343215
    warc_compressed_bytes: 34726906
    doc_rate: 0.46
    kb_rate: 134.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2015 December 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 January 17
    crawl: 191947
    start_date: 2016-01-17T16:55:00Z
    original_start_date: 2016-01-17T16:55:00Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-01-22T17:27:17Z
    end_date: 2016-01-22T16:56:58Z
    elapsed_ms: 432114027
    discovered_count: 573952
    novel_count: 20681
    duplicate_count: 273347
    queued_count: 279924
    downloaded_count: 294028
    download_failures: 181
    warc_revisit_count: 273342
    warc_url_count: 293928
    total_data_in_kbs: 63947333
    duplicate_bytes: 64312716410
    warc_compressed_bytes: 176478309
    doc_rate: 0.68
    kb_rate: 147.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 January 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 March 17
    crawl: 201840
    Crawl Rules
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ualbanysports.com (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for library.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for alumni.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for asrc.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for atmos.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for bioinformatics.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cela.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for choose.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cs.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for csda.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for imls.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for www.ctg.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cwig.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for events.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for hr.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for ibl.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for illiad.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for liblogs.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for libguides.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for scholarsarchive.library.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for listserv.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for m.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for omega.math.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for mumford.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for nyjm.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for pdp.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for resnet.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for cyberphysics.rit.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for rna.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for slsc.albany.edu (last updated 2017-05-19)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uaems.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for uapps.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    Ignore Robots.txt for wiki.albany.edu (last updated 2016-02-11)
    start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-03-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-03-22T18:02:10Z
    end_date: 2016-03-22T16:56:57Z
    elapsed_ms: 432107388
    discovered_count: 639552
    novel_count: 138564
    duplicate_count: 332568
    queued_count: 168420
    downloaded_count: 471132
    download_failures: 1411433
    warc_revisit_count: 332563
    warc_url_count: 471037
    total_data_in_kbs: 116820623
    duplicate_bytes: 113225737713
    warc_compressed_bytes: 765920585
    doc_rate: 1.09
    kb_rate: 270.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 March 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 April 17
    crawl: 207692
    start_date: 2016-04-17T16:55:13Z
    original_start_date: 2016-04-17T16:55:13Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-04-22T22:29:09Z
    end_date: 2016-04-22T18:00:08Z
    elapsed_ms: 435852385
    discovered_count: 7165982
    novel_count: 582992
    duplicate_count: 879835
    queued_count: 5703155
    downloaded_count: 1462827
    download_failures: 284
    warc_revisit_count: 879824
    warc_url_count: 1462700
    total_data_in_kbs: 227675763
    duplicate_bytes: 214936501775
    warc_compressed_bytes: 813502772
    doc_rate: 3.36
    kb_rate: 522.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 April 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 April 25
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 May 17
    crawl: 212937
    start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    original_start_date: 2016-05-17T16:55:02Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-05-24T10:38:52Z
    end_date: 2016-05-22T22:20:27Z
    elapsed_ms: 451503421
    discovered_count: 8685839
    novel_count: 568136
    duplicate_count: 1043240
    queued_count: 7074463
    downloaded_count: 1611376
    download_failures: 229
    warc_revisit_count: 1043205
    warc_url_count: 1611247
    total_data_in_kbs: 246906729
    duplicate_bytes: 230750229955
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2352496320
    doc_rate: 3.57
    kb_rate: 546.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 May 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 June 1
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 June 3
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 June 17
    crawl: 220038
    start_date: 2016-06-17T16:55:03Z
    original_start_date: 2016-06-17T16:55:03Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-06-23T01:46:32Z
    end_date: 2016-06-22T19:28:00Z
    elapsed_ms: 441165235
    discovered_count: 8887536
    novel_count: 557229
    duplicate_count: 1067492
    queued_count: 7262815
    downloaded_count: 1624721
    download_failures: 247
    warc_revisit_count: 1067450
    warc_url_count: 1624592
    total_data_in_kbs: 251943396
    duplicate_bytes: 239433481575
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1787914405
    doc_rate: 3.68
    kb_rate: 571.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 June 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 June 30
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 July 17
    crawl: 225859
    start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    original_start_date: 2016-07-17T16:55:03Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-07-22T22:52:35Z
    end_date: 2016-07-22T17:55:28Z
    elapsed_ms: 435383503
    discovered_count: 6792375
    novel_count: 212820
    duplicate_count: 1098346
    queued_count: 5481209
    downloaded_count: 1311166
    download_failures: 256
    warc_revisit_count: 1098317
    warc_url_count: 1311042
    total_data_in_kbs: 212249210
    duplicate_bytes: 207609316437
    warc_compressed_bytes: 675349961
    doc_rate: 3.01
    kb_rate: 487.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 July 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 July 30
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 August 17
    crawl: 231044
    Block host dev.library.albany.edu
    start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    original_start_date: 2016-08-17T16:58:06Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-08-23T01:20:50Z
    end_date: 2016-08-22T23:33:45Z
    elapsed_ms: 455703830
    discovered_count: 1189467
    novel_count: 184079
    duplicate_count: 736427
    queued_count: 268961
    downloaded_count: 920506
    download_failures: 267
    warc_revisit_count: 736404
    warc_url_count: 920384
    total_data_in_kbs: 202254345
    duplicate_bytes: 198029314926
    warc_compressed_bytes: 397770039
    doc_rate: 2.02
    kb_rate: 443.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 August 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 September 2
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 September 17
    crawl: 236726
    start_date: 2016-09-17T16:55:32Z
    original_start_date: 2016-09-17T16:55:32Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-09-22T19:45:41Z
    end_date: 2016-09-22T17:03:18Z
    elapsed_ms: 432208662
    discovered_count: 1414002
    novel_count: 188377
    duplicate_count: 898376
    queued_count: 327249
    downloaded_count: 1086753
    download_failures: 287
    warc_revisit_count: 898345
    warc_url_count: 1086634
    total_data_in_kbs: 205611728
    duplicate_bytes: 200652210118
    warc_compressed_bytes: 309191153
    doc_rate: 2.51
    kb_rate: 475.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 September 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 October 17
    crawl: 243096
    start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    original_start_date: 2016-10-17T16:56:12Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-10-22T20:32:46Z
    end_date: 2016-10-22T17:07:30Z
    elapsed_ms: 432270469
    discovered_count: 1819420
    novel_count: 557303
    duplicate_count: 900445
    queued_count: 361672
    downloaded_count: 1457748
    download_failures: 296
    warc_revisit_count: 900407
    warc_url_count: 1457649
    total_data_in_kbs: 215568357
    duplicate_bytes: 201221539907
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1485925187
    doc_rate: 3.37
    kb_rate: 498.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 October 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 November 17
    crawl: 249672
    start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    original_start_date: 2016-11-17T16:57:23Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-11-22T23:26:30Z
    end_date: 2016-11-22T18:15:59Z
    elapsed_ms: 436686458
    discovered_count: 6455397
    novel_count: 904107
    duplicate_count: 647491
    queued_count: 4903799
    downloaded_count: 1551598
    warc_revisit_count: 647445
    warc_url_count: 1551482
    total_data_in_kbs: 234676600
    duplicate_bytes: 166348006398
    warc_compressed_bytes: 22645478722
    doc_rate: 3.55
    kb_rate: 537.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 November 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 December 17
    crawl: 255339
    start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    original_start_date: 2016-12-17T16:54:59Z
    processing_end_date: 2016-12-22T23:02:36Z
    end_date: 2016-12-22T17:39:38Z
    elapsed_ms: 434651176
    discovered_count: 5605147
    novel_count: 672626
    duplicate_count: 721586
    queued_count: 4210935
    downloaded_count: 1394212
    warc_revisit_count: 721559
    warc_url_count: 1394095
    total_data_in_kbs: 173161585
    duplicate_bytes: 152072050167
    warc_compressed_bytes: 4226018506
    doc_rate: 3.21
    kb_rate: 398.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2016 December 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 January 17
    crawl: 261028
    start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    original_start_date: 2017-01-17T17:03:42Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-01-23T00:48:05Z
    end_date: 2017-01-22T19:31:33Z
    elapsed_ms: 440845477
    discovered_count: 6856243
    novel_count: 810250
    duplicate_count: 844972
    queued_count: 5201021
    downloaded_count: 1655222
    download_failures: 351
    warc_revisit_count: 844920
    warc_url_count: 1655090
    total_data_in_kbs: 260833049
    duplicate_bytes: 210669517964
    warc_compressed_bytes: 15598206209
    doc_rate: 3.75
    kb_rate: 591.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 January 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 February 17
    crawl: 267806
    start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    original_start_date: 2017-02-17T16:57:01Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-02-22T23:52:19Z
    end_date: 2017-02-22T17:57:15Z
    elapsed_ms: 435595208
    discovered_count: 6181071
    novel_count: 757736
    duplicate_count: 820126
    queued_count: 4603209
    downloaded_count: 1577862
    download_failures: 339
    warc_revisit_count: 820090
    warc_url_count: 1577729
    total_data_in_kbs: 257873727
    duplicate_bytes: 232995142726
    warc_compressed_bytes: 5661819855
    doc_rate: 3.62
    kb_rate: 592.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 February 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 March 17
    crawl: 273971
    start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    original_start_date: 2017-03-17T16:55:07Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-03-22T22:25:00Z
    end_date: 2017-03-22T18:08:47Z
    elapsed_ms: 436406787
    discovered_count: 7409222
    novel_count: 690900
    duplicate_count: 1257496
    queued_count: 5460826
    downloaded_count: 1948396
    download_failures: 359
    warc_revisit_count: 1257455
    warc_url_count: 1948270
    total_data_in_kbs: 266864045
    duplicate_bytes: 245675593330
    warc_compressed_bytes: 1581675727
    doc_rate: 4.46
    kb_rate: 611.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 March 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 April 17
    crawl: 291352
    start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    original_start_date: 2017-04-17T16:55:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-04-22T22:22:12Z
    end_date: 2017-04-22T17:55:16Z
    elapsed_ms: 435220728
    discovered_count: 8221578
    novel_count: 736180
    duplicate_count: 1311488
    queued_count: 6173910
    downloaded_count: 2047668
    download_failures: 335
    warc_revisit_count: 1311435
    warc_url_count: 2047538
    total_data_in_kbs: 284745035
    duplicate_bytes: 261915565851
    warc_compressed_bytes: 2411311996
    doc_rate: 4.7
    kb_rate: 654.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 April 17
  - University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 May 17
    crawl: 301465
    Host Rule Type C CONTAINS meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search? (last updated 2017-05-11)
    start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    original_start_date: 2017-05-17T16:55:17Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-05-23T00:29:43Z
    end_date: 2017-05-22T21:46:25Z
    elapsed_ms: 449440076
    discovered_count: 2923335
    novel_count: 388249
    duplicate_count: 1238165
    queued_count: 1296921
    downloaded_count: 1626414
    download_failures: 336
    warc_revisit_count: 1238113
    warc_url_count: 1626286
    total_data_in_kbs: 265327774
    duplicate_bytes: 251274786133
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3306915146
    kb_rate: 590.0
  - WARC file for University at Albany - SUNY - Office of Facilities Management, 2017 May 17